字幕修改自mylittlekaraoke,感谢@一条小羊dog
字幕样式部分来自EQCN，部分修改自潮汐字幕社
翻译来自EQCN
The Super Duper Party Pony
那热情奔放派对小马数我是第一
That pony is me
本字幕采用知识共享-署名-相同方式共享 4.0 国际许可协议进行许可
http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/deed.zh
I always knew that was
我知道这份热爱早已深入生命里
The kind of pony I would be
Me too!
我也是
Come on, ponies! Who here likes to party?
来吧 小马们 谁想来开派对？
Ha-ha! You do, I can tell!
我看你很想
When I was but a little colt
回想我当年小时候
I just wanted to play
我总想玩开心
Like me!
我也是
But everypony told me
可大家全说什么
"Cheese, that fun just wastes the day"
“一寸光阴一寸金”
as if
无聊
But when I threw a party
但当我开起派对
And I busted out some moves
跳起独门的舞蹈
Uh-huh!
The ponies finally saw the light
才点亮他们心中热情
And got into the groove
一起来热闹
You know it!
就是嘛
The Super Duper Party Pony
那热情奔放派对小马数我是第一
That pony is me
And me!
还有我
You'll never meet another
只要开起派对 没谁能与我相比
Party pony quite like Cheese!
Uh, Pinkie?
还有...萍琪？
Hey, good lookin', want some mayonnaise?
帅哥 来点蛋黄酱吗？
My parties are all off the hook
我的派对疯狂至极
I never plan them by the book
从不按套路和常理
I start out fun, then whoopsie daisy
笑过之后有惊奇
Everybody just gets crazy!
疯就疯到一起
Bored of snacks made by your mom?
妈妈的甜点会吃腻
How 'bout a giant party bomb?
那来个炸弹装惊喜
Huge piñatas filled with cake
装满蛋糕的皮纳塔
Or dive into my fruit punch lake!
或者跳进果汁湖里
Geronimo!
深水炸弹
The Super Duper Party Pony
那热情奔放派对小马数我是第一
That pony is me
You'll never meet another
只要开起派对 没谁能与我相比
Party pony quite like Cheese
C'mon, kid, take it for a spin!
来来来 孩子 上去兜一圈
Golly! Thanks, mister!
真棒谢谢叔叔
Oh, when I throw a Cheese party
当我开起派对时
Be sure to not be lame
可别老掉牙
And miss my pie fights, wacky kites
飞派大战 古怪风筝
And streamers in your mane
彩带满头插
Fizzy drinks, Hawaiian shirts
气泡饮料花衬衫
And brie fondue delight
蛋奶一锅端
You know that with Cheese Sandwich
有我起司三明治
You'll be partying all night!
彻夜都能狂欢
C'mon, everypony!
一起来吧
Let's party down with Cheese!
来和起司开派对
You're really a certified party pony?
你真是专业的派对主持吗？
That's right! That's my guarantee!
当然是 如假包换
The Super Duper Party Pony
那热情奔放派对小马数我是第一
That pony is me
But what about the Super Party Pony named Pinkie?
可谁还记得热爱派对的小马萍琪？